Komodo vs. Cobra is a horror, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Jim Wynorski.
A team of environmentalists, including a reporter, her camera man, and an environmentalist's
famous girlfriend charter a boat and with the captain, sail to a military island.
They suspect the island is hosting to illegal activities.
Upon arrival, however, they find no one.
They finally reach a deserted house, where they find Dr.
Susan Richardson, who tells them that everyone on the
island is dead, including her father.
Richardson's team were working on a compound that could make edible plants grow to
super size, however the military intervened with plans of their own.
They wanted to test the compound's effects on animals, and
proceeded to feed it to several komodo dragons and cobras.
Capt. Michael A. Stoddard, played by Michael Paré.
Dr. Susan Richardson, played by Michelle Borth.
Jerry Ryan, played by Ryan McTavish.
Carrie Evans, played by Renee Talbert.
Sandra Crescent, played by Jerri Manthey.
Ted, played by Ted Monte.
Cobra, also referred to as KVC, is a 2005 American
television film directed by Jim Wynorski.
It is Wynorski's sequel to his 2004 film Curse of the Komodo.
Wynroski says the first film "all turned out rather fun; so
much so that they asked me to do a sequel.
I said I would do it provided they sent myself and the entire
cast to Hawaii to film it…which they did."
The film explores themes of island, giant snake,
scientist, giant animal, komodo dragon.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.